(Penny:)It's out of order.
(Woman:)Yes, I can read the sign.
I'm just pondering the implications.
(Penny:)I think it implies
that the elevator doesn't work.
(Woman:)Again, I can read the sign.
But the sign and tape are covered
with a layer of dust which indicates...
(Woman:)...the elevator has been nonfunctional
for an amount of time...
(Woman:)...which suggests either a remarkable
passivity among the...
(Woman:)...I assume 24 to 36 residents
of this building...
(Woman:)...based on the number of mailboxes and
given typical urban population density...
(Woman:)...or a shared delusion of functionality.
(Penny:)You must be Leonard's mother.
(Leonard's Mother:)Oh, I don't know if I must be, but yes.
- Uh, I'm Penny, I'm his neighbor.
- Oh, Dr. Beverly Hofstadter.
(Penny:)Oh, nice to meet you.
(Beverley:)Oh, you're a hand shaker. Interesting.